Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 3: Boxes 127-191
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 3: Boxes 127-191
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 134, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Amalgamated Laundry Workers Bulletin, 1956-1960 (Box 134, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol. IV, no. 48-49, 53 (1956-1957)
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 134, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Board of arbitration for the agreements between the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America and Chicago Clothing Manufacturers; decision of Dec. 22, 1919; decision of April 14, 1921 (preliminary edition), 1919-1921 (Box 134, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Causes of industrial peace under collective bargaining, 1949; Publication (Box 134, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: The Hart, Schaffner & Marx labor agreement, 1916; Publication (Box 134, Folder 4)
    Author: Hart, Schaffner & Marx
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 134, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: a report on the realization of a dream, 1954-1955 (Box 134, Folder 5)
    Notes: Biennial report
  - Item 2: A stitch in time, 1950; Publication (Box 134, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Amalgamated Cooperative Housing, 1954-1955 (Box 134, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Handbook of information on Group Life Insurance and Group Accident, 1944; Publication (Box 134, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Handbook of information on Group Life Insurance and Group Accident, 1946; Publication (Box 134, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Handbook of information on Group Life Insurance and Group Accident, 1950; Publication (Box 134, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Insurance program for ACWA members in the Cotton Garment and Allied Industries, 1964; Publication (Box 134, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Labor helps itself, Amalgamated Welfare Plan, 1954; Publication (Box 134, Folder 5)
    Author: Eleanor Astor
  - Item 9: Security, the central issue [the Health and Welfare Program of the Amalgamated Clothing Workers], 1952; Publication (Box 134, Folder 5)
    Author: William P. Gottlieb
  - Item 10: The Amalgamated Health Centers, 1954-1955 (Box 134, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: The Amalgamated Welfare Plan, 1954-1955 (Box 134, Folder 5)
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 134, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Venture in child care: The Baltimore Regional Joint Board, Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, Health and Welfare Fund, 1968; Publication (Box 134, Folder 6)
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 134, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Biography of Sidney Hillman, General President, Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1944; Publication (Box 134, Folder 7)
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 134, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Boston Joint Board Review of 1946, 1947; Publication (Box 134, Folder 8)
    Notes: Vol. 1, no.1 (Jan. 1947)
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 134, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: John E. Williams: an appreciation with selections from his writings, 1930; Publication (Box 134, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Amalgamated Centre, the tailor re-tailored: a story of surging humanity, 1910-1928., Publication (Box 134, Folder 9)
    Author: Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America. Chicago Joint Board
  - Item 3: The Union you've joined: Chicago Joint Board, Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America (C.I.O.), how it came to be, what its is, what it stands for, 1947; Publication (Box 134, Folder 9)
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 134, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The Cincinnati clothing workers, 1913-1938. A quarter of a century of endeavors and achievement, Publication (Box 134, Folder 10)
    Author: Jack Kroll
  - Item 2: The Amalgamated in Cincinnati; a record of struggle and achievement, 1928; Publication (Box 134, Folder 10)
    Author: Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America. Cincinnati joint board
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 134, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Our union: how and why, 1938; Publication (Box 134, Folder 11)
    Author: Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America.
  - Item 2: The left wing in the garment unions, 1927; Publication (Box 134, Folder 11)
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 135, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: In the Supreme Court of the United States, October term, 1954, no. 173, Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America and Cleveland Joint Board of the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, Petitioners, v. The Richman Brothers Company, Respondent, on writ of, Publication (Box 135, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: In the Supreme Court of the United States, October term, 1954, no. 173, Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America and Cleveland Joint Board of the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, Petitioners, v. The Richman Brothers Company, Respondent, on writ of, Publication (Box 135, Folder 1)
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 135, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Public speaking course, 1939; Publication (Box 135, Folder 2)
    Notes: Workshop materials
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 135, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Amalgamated Correspondence Courses, 1941; Publication (Box 135, Folder 3)
    Notes: Issued by Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, Dept. of Cultural Activities
  - Item 2: Labor in American History, 1940; Publication (Box 135, Folder 3)
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 135, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Labor and Culture: A magazine of Union labor education - (Fall Issue), 1941; Publication (Box 135, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Labor in American History, 1940; Publication (Box 135, Folder 4)
    Notes: Workshop materials. Copy 2
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 135, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining, 1939; Publication (Box 135, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Delegates Handbook - Regional Conference on Cultural Activities, Springfield, Oct. 1938, Publication (Box 135, Folder 5)
    Notes: Conference materials
  - Item 3: Democracy-Aims and practices, 1939; Publication (Box 135, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Unionism - a way of life, The ACWA Program of Cultural Activities, 1939; Publication (Box 135, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Economics of the Men's Clothing Industry, 1939; Publication (Box 135, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Labor in American History, 1939; Publication (Box 135, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Practical problems in trade unionism, 1939; Publication (Box 135, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Amalgamated cultural activities, 1940, Publication (Box 135, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Amalgamated Swing - words and music by Irving Gaynor Neiman, 1939; Publication (Box 135, Folder 5)
    Author: Irving Gaynor Neiman
    Notes: Sheet music
  - Item 10: Collective Bargaining, 1940; Publication (Box 135, Folder 5)
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: ACWA on trial, 1926; Publication (Box 136, Folder 1)
    Author: John Huber
  - Item 2: 27 questions and answers on the open shop movement, 1920; Publication (Box 136, Folder 1)
    Author: Paul Blanshard
  - Item 3: A proposal for an unemployment fund in the men's clothing industry, 1922; Publication (Box 136, Folder 1)
    Author: Leo Wolman
  - Item 4: Labor in transition, 1914-1924: a retrospect and the outlook, Publication (Box 136, Folder 1)
    Notes: Amalgamated education pamphlets series no. 9
  - Item 5: Readings for May First and thoughts for May second, 1923; Publication (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Recent developments in trade-unionism, 1921; Publication (Box 136, Folder 1)
    Author: Soule, George Henry
  - Item 7: So this is the Amalgamated!, 1924; Publication (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: The message of internationalism, 1923; Publication (Box 136, Folder 1)
    Author: Joseph Schlossberg
  - Item 9: We, bits of the story of the struggle for freedom: why we are, what we are, how we are?, 1925; Publication (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Where workers rule, 1922; Publication (Box 136, Folder 1)
    Author: Leo Hartmann
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 136, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Amalgamated Clothing Workers Daily Calendar: the daily handbook of facts and ideas, 1925; Publication (Box 136, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: The Amalgamated illustrated Almanac, 1924; Publication (Box 136, Folder 2)
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 136, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Labor between the wars, 1941; Publication (Box 136, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Sing Amalgamated!, 1944; Publication (Box 136, Folder 3)
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 136, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Bibliography of material available through the Education Department, 1948; Publication (Box 136, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Source material for education directors, 1948; Publication (Box 136, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Supplement to the March 1948 Bibliography of the Education Department, Publication (Box 136, Folder 4)
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 136, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: ACWA film catalogue, 1949; Publication (Box 136, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Hi There!, I'm your Shop Steward, 1950; Publication (Box 136, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: How to conduct your union meeting, 1949; Publication (Box 136, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Meet the Amalgamated, 1950; Publication (Box 136, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Mimeo handbook, 1949; Publication (Box 136, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: The National Education Dept. Presents Services for you., 1950; Publication (Box 136, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: When you buy men's clothes look for the guarantee, 1949; Publication (Box 136, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: You are now a shop steward, 1954; Publication (Box 136, Folder 5)
    Author: Mary L. Elkuss and William Elkuss
    Notes: Draft, not for general distribution
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 136, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Hi There!, I'm your Shop Steward, 1953; Publication (Box 136, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Insurance program for clothing workers, 1953; Publication (Box 136, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Your dues dollar at work, 1953; Publication (Box 136, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Amalgamated song book, 1952; Publication (Box 136, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Bienvenidos a vuestra Union, 1953; Publication (Box 136, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: The CIO: History, theory, prospects, 1938; Publication (Box 136, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Welcome to your union, 1953; Publication (Box 136, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: You are now a shop steward, 1954; Publication (Box 136, Folder 6)
    Notes: Draft, not for general distribution. Copy 2
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 136, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Inside SFA, 1949; Publication (Box 136, Folder 7)
    Notes: vol. 1, no. 1(1949:June 1)
  - Item 2: Where we stand!, 1954; Publication (Box 136, Folder 7)
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: 1968 is a crucial election year, Publication (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Do you want more unemployment, Publication (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Your dues build the union, Publication (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Your dues dollar, Publication (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Your dues dollar at work, Publication (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: 13th Annual Training Institute., 1961; Publication (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: How union grievance procedure works, Publication (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Paperback books available at one-third discount, 1962; Publication (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Planning local Union education programs, 1955; Publication (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Sus Cuotas levantan la union, Publication (Box 137, Folder 1)
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 137, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: A new member's guide to the ACWA, 1955-1957 (Box 137, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Conducting your Union meeting, 1955-1957 (Box 137, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Insurance program for ACW members in the Cotton Garment and Allied Industries, 1955-1957 (Box 137, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Welcome to your union, 1955-1957 (Box 137, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: ACWA film library, 1955-1957 (Box 137, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: How to help win the $1.25 an hour Federal minimum wage and extended coverage, Publication (Box 137, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: This is your new member kit, Publication (Box 137, Folder 2)
    Notes: Information packet
  - Item 8: Your national per capita dollar at work, 1955-1957 (Box 137, Folder 2)
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 137, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: correspondence, 1951; Publication (Box 137, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: correspondence, 1962; Publication (Box 137, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: News Letter from the ACWA Education Department, 1949-1954 (Box 137, Folder 3)
    Notes: 1949 (Dec.); 1950 (Jan.-Feb., June, July, Dec); 1951 (Feb-Mar, Aug.-Sept., Nov.); 1952 (Oct.); 1953 (Aug.); 1954 (Mar.)
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 137, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: correspondence, 1950-1961 (Box 137, Folder 4)
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 137, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: A union fights mental illness, 1964; Publication (Box 137, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Excerpts from testimony by Morris A. Brand, 1952; Publication (Box 137, Folder 5)
    Author: Morris A. Brand
  - Item 3: Health security by union action: A report on the Sidney Hillman Health Center of New York., 1952; Publication (Box 137, Folder 5)
    Author: Elden La Mar
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 137, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Helping blue-collar workers in trouble: a report of a labor-mental health conference, New York City, 1967., 1969; Publication (Box 137, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Security, the central issue, 1952; Publication (Box 137, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: The Amalgamated Health Centers: a report on the realization of a dream, 1954-1955 (Box 137, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: The picture that came to life, 1951; Publication (Box 137, Folder 6)
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 137, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Legislative News, 1950-1969 (Box 137, Folder 7)
    Notes: Assorted issues
  - Item 2: Legislative News, 1950-1969 (Box 137, Folder 7)
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 137, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Legislative Action Bulletin, 1950-1969 (Box 137, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Legislative News, 1950-1969 (Box 137, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Sidney Hillman, Publication (Box 137, Folder 8)
    Notes: Article about his life
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 137, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: A successful experiment in unemployment insurance, 1931; Publication (Box 137, Folder 9)
    Author: Sidney Hillman
    Notes: Reprinted from the Annals of the American Academy of Political and Social Science.
  - Item 2: Labor in the United States, Publication (Box 137, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Sidney Hillman, 1887-1946, 1947; Publication (Box 137, Folder 9)
    Author: A. H. Raskin
  - Item 4: The Sidney Hillman Foundation: a record of service to the community, 1954; Publication (Box 137, Folder 9)
    Author: Sidney Hillman Foundation
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 138, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: 45 Years Amalgamated - 1915-1960, Publication (Box 138, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Rochester History, 1960; Publication (Box 138, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol. XXII, No. 3(1960:July)
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Ever forward: a short history of the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, AFL-CIO, 1962; Publication (Box 138, Folder 2)
    Author: Vera Miller
  - Item 2: Ever forward: forty years of progress; a short history, 1955; Publication (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: History, Structure and function of the Amalgamated, 1948; Publication (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Sidney Hillman: labor statesman, 1948; Publication (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: The Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America - A Twenty-two year history, 1936; Publication (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: The Amalgamated illustrated Almanac, 1924; Publication (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: The So. Jersey Joint Board A.C.W.A. - Our story (12th Biennial Convention, Atlantic City, 1938), Publication (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: A brief history of the Amalgamated: Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, AFL-CIO, CLC, 1975; Publication (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Bread and roses: the story of the rise of the shirtworkers: two eventful years, 1933-1934, 1935; Publication (Box 138, Folder 2)
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 138, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: application for Retirement Benefits, Publication (Box 138, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Chart of Amalgamated Insurance and Retirement Benefits, 1958; Publication (Box 138, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Group Insurance Benefit Information, 1946; Publication (Box 138, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Retirement Benefits Information, 1951; Publication (Box 138, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: The Amalgamated Life Insurance Company, Inc., Publication (Box 138, Folder 3)
    Notes: Policy information and application
  - Item 6: The employee benefit program of the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1947; Publication (Box 138, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: The welfare program of the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1954; Publication (Box 138, Folder 3)
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 138, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Inter-Office Memorandum, 1984; Publication (Box 138, Folder 4)
    Author: Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union
  - Item 2: The ADVANCE, 1951; Publication (Box 138, Folder 4)
    Notes: Oct. 15, 1951
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 138, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Ever forward: forty years of progress; a short history, 1955; Publication (Box 138, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: These twenty years-- and the next: 1914-1934-1954: a trip through ACWA, history and future., Publication (Box 138, Folder 5)
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Bibliography to articles, books and source material on the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1922; Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Hourly table of wages from $9 to $50, 1939; Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Proceedings of the First Convention of the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1914; Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Styles in strikes, 1929; Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
    Author: Beulah Amidon
  - Item 5: The case of the union as stated by observers: in the press, in the court, in a normal market., 1921; Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: The Russian-American Industrial Corporation: report to the Board of Directors and stockholders on conditions in Soviet Russia and contracts, 1923; Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: The Russian-American Industrial Corporation for aid in the economic reconstruction of Russia: prospectus, 1922; Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
    Author: Russian-American Industrial Corporation
  - Item 8: The SURVEY, 1919; Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
    Notes: Sept. 13, 1919
  - Item 9: Unemployment agreement between members of the Chicago Industrial Federation of Clothing Manufacturers and the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America: October 1923., Publication (Box 139, Folder 1)
    Author: Chicago Industrial Federation of Clothing Manufacturers
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: 1937-1957 The remarkable twenty year history, Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Amalgamated Laundry Workers Bulletin, 1954-1955 (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Notes: Vol. III, no.2, 5-8, 10-11 (1954); Vol. IV, no. 1, 3, 46 (1955); Vol.IX, no. 45 (1955)
  - Item 3: Amalgamated Laundry Workers handbook, Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Author: Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America. Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint Board
  - Item 4: Facts about your union, 1939; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Handbook of information on Group Life Insurance and Group Accident, 1950; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Laundry Workers Joint Board, Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, Income and Expense, 1952; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: The Amalgamated Laundry Workers Joint BoardComo funciona, como lo protg a usted, sus derechos, sus deberes, 1959; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: The Amalgamated Laundry Workers, Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, AFL-CIO: how it functions, how it protects you, your rights, your responsibilities, Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: The Journal of the Laundry Workers Joint Board of Greater New York 10th Anniv., 1947; Publication (Box 139, Folder 2)
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 139, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Justice on the job before you vote FEPC or else, 1948; Publication (Box 139, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Statement in support of amendment to the Fair Labor Standards Act, 1948; Publication (Box 139, Folder 3)
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 139, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Bibliography of the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1926; Publication (Box 139, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Information please! Thirty-three questions and answers about your union, Publication (Box 139, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Mary stays after school or What this union's about, 1939; Publication (Box 139, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Move on!: thirty thousand clothing workers on the go, Publication (Box 139, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: The Builder, 1938-1939 (Box 139, Folder 4)
    Notes: Issues
  - Item 6: The unemployment insurance plan of the Amalgamated Clothing Worker, 1932; Publication (Box 139, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Union Builder, 1937; Publication (Box 139, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol. 1, no. 2 (1937:Dec.)
  - Item 8: Union rules of order: the laws of parliamentary procedure as they apply to local union and committee meetings, 1937; Publication (Box 139, Folder 4)
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 139, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Drugs, the prices are right, 1966-1967 (Box 139, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: An open letter to SIU Atlantic and Gulf District Members, 1965; Publication (Box 139, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Organized labor outlines, 1966-1967 (Box 139, Folder 5)
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 139, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Annual Entertainment and Dance - New York Clothing Cutters Union, 1934; Publication (Box 139, Folder 6)
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 139, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Souvenir JournalTwenty-Five Years, the story of Cutters Local Big Four, 1938; Publication (Box 139, Folder 7)
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 139, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: 400-4-Sight, 1947-1948 (Box 139, Folder 8)
    Notes: vol.I, no.1, 6-10, vol.II, no.2-3
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 139, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Pictorial union dictionary: an illustrated guide to terms used in the labor movement, 1943; Publication (Box 139, Folder 9)
    Author: Inter-Union Institute for Labor and Democracy.
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 139, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Needle and thread, 1915-1960: 45 years Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1961; Publication (Box 139, Folder 10)
    Author: Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America. New York Joint Board
  - Item 2: Sidney Hillman Health Center Bulletin, 1953; Publication (Box 139, Folder 10)
    Notes: vol.1, no.3 (May, 1953)
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 139, Folder 11)